# **ROBERT S. HARRIS**

# **UI/UX Designer & Developer**

Skilled in the UX design processes and methodologies from design thinking, strategy, discovery and research to creating sitemaps, wireframes, visual designs, and prototypes to usability testing and delivery. Also, Extensive experience with CSS3, HTML5, Adobe CC, and JavaScript. Passionate human-centered design advocate who is committed to discovering the problems that the business and users are facing and designing the architecture, interactions, user flows and visual design of the product.

# Work Experience

**WorldShaker Interactive, Inc. /** Product Designer I UI Developer

SEPT 1998 - PRESENT, BROOKLYN, NY

Worked as a consultant on the production, re-design, UI development, integration, wireframing and A/B testing. Sony Music - Various artists Drupal sites, Dow Jones - wsj.com, Saks Fifth Avenue - saks.com, Cline Davis Mann - Pfizer, TV Guide Online - tvguideonline.com, Interactive Media Associates - touchtunes.com, Turner Broadcasting Inc. - **thefrisky.com**, Icon Nicholson, KBSP - bmwusa.com, CAHG - Omnicom Media Group.

**KPMG /** Contract Web Producer & Designer APRIL 2017 - MAY 2020, MONTVALE NJ

Worked on the redesign and migration - SharePoint 2007 to 2013 - of KPMG's US Portal enterprise level site and KPMG's local offices. Interviewed stakeholders to gather data and insights on their business needs and goals for the teams. Produced the solutions for business units.

## Pershing - BNY Mellon / UI Developer

APRIL 2014 - DECEMBER 2015, JERSEY CITY, NJ

As a UI developer I was responsible for developing and building over 70 sites for the firm's finance and banking clients who used nettxinvestor.com. I also collaborated with the UX Design team and other stakeholders on the adaptive and ADA versions of the clients' sites.

Portfolio: <a href="www.worldshaker.com">www.worldshaker.com</a>
Email: <a href="mailto:rharris@worldshakler.com">rharris@worldshakler.com</a>
LinkedIn: <a href="mailto:linkedin.com/in/robertsharris">linkedin.com/in/robertsharris</a>

Cell: 646.620.4438

### Education

General Assembly / UXDI March 2021 - June 2021 Baruch College – CUNY BBA - Computer Information Systems - 2003

#### Skills

Design: UX Research, Wireframing, Usability Testing, Prototyping, Business Analysis

Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Material UI, SQL, React

Tools: Figma, Sketch, Photoshop, Premiere Pro, Miro, Mural, Visual Studio Code, Justinmind

#### **Activities**

Photography, Videography, Running, Fishing, Tennis, Cooking.